The birds from this tree can sing like different sounds from the world
Select the birds to listen them sing
Great! Press the button when you are ready
Ready!
Are you ready?
Drag the bird to the nest with the same sound, if you're not sure you can select the bird to listen his sound again
Great!
Listen to the sequence and remember which bird makes each sound
Listen to the sound and remember which bird makes the sound
Example
Forest
Beach
Congratulations!
Oh!
You didn't win a Kiwi
You won
Kiwis
Kiwi
PAUSE
OK
Keep Playing
Back to my Island