Look for this object in the beach
Look for this objects in the beach
Move the JOYSTICK forward and backward to move
Great! Now move the JOYSTICK to the sides to turn
Excellent! Now is time to find the object you were asked, move towards an arrow
The object will shine if you can pick it up! Press the GREEN BUTTON to grab it
Now you have an object in your bag
Go back to the Koala
Press the UP and DOWN ARROW to move
Great! Now press the LEFT or RIGHT ARROW to turn
The object will shine if you can pick it up! Press the SPACEBAR to grab it
You grabbed an object that you shouldn't, press it to drop it
You are missing some objects, go get them
Are you sure that you brought the correct objects?
Do you want to review what you were asked?
Wait I think you made a mistake
You picked up the correct objects
Excellent! Now help me find more things
Congratulations!
Oh!
You didn't win a Kiwi
You won
Kiwis
Kiwi
PAUSE
OK
Keep Playing
Back to my Island
READY
What to Search
Your Objects
You won!
Coconut
Coconuts
Opened coconut
Opened coconuts
Bucket
Buckets
Ring Frisbee
Ring Frisbees
Circle Frisbee
Circle Fribees
Blue Shovel
Blue Shovels
Red Shovel
Red Shovels
Green Shovel
Green Shovels
Big beach ball
Big beach balls
Banana
Bananas
Banana peel
Banana peels
Rake with five teeth
Rakes with five teeth
Rake with three teeth
Rakes with three teeth
Wood chair
Wood chairs
Plastic chair
Plastic chairs
Small beach ball
Small beach balls
Flying seagull
Flying seagulls
Crab
Crabs
Seagull on the floor
Seagulls on the floor
Open shell
Open shells
Closed shell
Closed shells
Bucket without handle
Buckets without handle
Shovel
Shovels
Beach ball
Beach balls
Coconut
Coconuts
Bucket
Buckets
Shell
Shells